ILGWU Education Department, Kitty Krupat Papers 5780/138
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Education Department, Kitty Krupat Papers
1974-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Krupat, Kitty
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/138
14 cubic feet
14 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Krupat's papers include correspondence, memoranda, reports, and financial records relating to the ILGWU's independent and collaborative education projects, including the Worker-Family Education Program, the Joint Union-University Committee on Labor Education, and the Consortium for Worker Education, as well as numerous trainings, conferences, and seminars. Also included in the files are materials from local unions and regional departments of the ILGWU, files on the Internationals' conventions, and reports to the General Executive Board.
5520819
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
J. Woodward, August 26, 2009
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 15, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
From 1989 to 1995, Kitty Krupat was Director of Education Department of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Prior to working with the ILGWU, Krupat was on staff of the United Auto Workers (UAW).
Biographical / Historical
Local union's of the ILGWU established and maintained robust, ambitious educational departments early on in the international's history. As these groups grew in size and scope, the international office sought to coordinate and centralize educational programming for the union's members, culminating in the formation of the Educational Department in 1918.
The department's programming included courses at the Workers' University at the Washington Irving High School in New York City, lectures at Unity Centers and Unity Houses in the northeastern United States, and other events. The educational offerings of the International's Education Department were varied, as had been the education departments of the local unions, and included not only classes in labor studies but also courses in languages, music, and the arts. The ILGWU's 1937 musical "Pins and Needles" exemplified the diversity of the union's programs.
Directors of the Education Department, especially Fannia Cohn and Mark Starr, wrote extensively on the ILGWU's programs and worker education in general. Longtime director Gus Tyler not only directed the department, but also served as the ILGWU's on-staff scholar. In later years, the Education Department went beyond collaborating with other education organizations and arranging in-house programs to also supporting post-secondary education for union members and their families.
Scope and Contents
The Education Department records document activities across the entire period of the department's existence, with the bulk of the records covering the 1970s and 1990s. It contains papers from directors of the Education Department: Fannia Cohn, Mark Starr, Gus Tyler, and Kitty Krupat.
The earliest documentation of the department's work is found in the Fannia Cohn papers (5780/049, 5780/049 P); these contain correspondence, subject files, speeches, photographs, and printed material from her work as director of the Educational Department. A microfilm copy of the Fannia Cohn papers held at the New York Public Library (5998 mf) complements the Kheel Center's holdings. Documentation of the work of another longtime leader of the Education Department, Mark Starr, is contained in these records (5780/166, 5780/166 PUBS), as well as in a related collection from Starr on worker education programs (5243).
Documentation of the work of Gus Tyler, who led the merged Education and Political Department after Mark Starr's retirement in 1960, is also contained in the ILGWU records (5780/052, 5780/088, 5780/096). Tyler's papers are complemented by those of Assistant Director Jasper Peyton (5780/086) and Special Projects Coordinator Beverly Shulman (5780/106). These collections contain routine correspondence and memoranda, reports, materials relating to training institutes, seminars, and conferences, and printed material.
The papers of Kitty Krupat, who was serving as Education Director at the time of the ILGWU/ACTWU merger in 1995, constitute the entirety of Education Department records from the 1990s. They include correspondence, memoranda, reports, and financial records relating to the ILGWU's independent and collaborative education projects, including the Worker-Family Education Program, the Joint Union-University Committee on Labor Education, and the Consortium for Worker Education, as well as numerous trainings, conferences, and seminars. Also included in the files are materials from local unions and regional departments of the ILGWU, files on the Internationals' conventions, and reports to the General Executive Board.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/106: ILGWU Education Department, Beverly Shulman Papers 5780/166: ILGWU Education Department Records 5780/166 PUBS: ILGWU Education Department Publications 5780/086: ILGWU Education Department, Jasper Peyton Papers 5780/049: ILGWU Education Department, Fannia Cohn Papers 5780/049 P: ILGWU Education Department, Fannia Cohn Photographs
Women's clothing industry--United States.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--United States.; Clothing workers--United States.; Industrial relations--United States.; Krupat, Kitty.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Education Department
5520819
- Education Directors: Education Directors and Representatives - National/Int'l organs (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Education Directors: Education Directors Program for 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Education Directors: Proposal for an Education Director's Forum (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Worker-Family Education Program: Graduation 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Worker-Family Education Program: Marcus and Wiesen, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Worker-Family Education Program: Worker Education - ESL Classes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Worker-Family Education Program: Worker Family Education Eligibility Rules and Procedures (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Worker-Family Education Program: Worker Center, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Worker-Family Education Program: WFEP Billing Records, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Worker-Family Education Program: WFEP 1991-1992 Budget (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Worker-Family Education Program: WFEP Budget and Background 1993/4, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Worker-Family Education Program: WFEP 1992-1993 Budget (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Worker-Family Education Program: WFEP Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Worker-Family Education Program: Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Worker-Family Education Program: News and Printed Articles, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Worker-Family Education Program: Workers of America Literacy Project, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Worker-Family Education Program: Workplace Literacy and the Nation's Unemployed Workers (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Education Planning Committee: Meeting Report 10/10-11/91, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Educational Projects: Annual Mid-west Summer Institute Chicago 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Educational Projects: ILGWU for Racial Armony, Children Art Contest, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Educational Projects: Organizers Institute, February 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ILGWU, GAC: G.A.C. October 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ILGWU, GAC: G.A.C. September 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ILGWU, GAC: G.A.C. September 24-25, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- ILGWU, GAC: G.A.C. March 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- ILGWU, GAC: G.A.C. Conference 1993 at Loews New York, October (Box 2, Folder 8)
- ILGWU, GAC: ILGWU Gral. Advisory Council, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- ILGWU, GAC: G.A.C. December 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- G.A.C. Feb. 1994 - Philadelphia (Box 2, Folder 11)
- G.A.C. Labor Management. Advisory Committee, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- GEB 1991: Report of the Benefit Funds Dept. to the GEB Chicago, Oct. 15-18 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Oct. 15-18, 1991
- GEB 1991: Report from the Political Dept. to the GEB Chicago, Oct. 15-18, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- GEB 1991: Report from the Associate Members to the GEB Chicago, Oct. 15-18, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- GEB 1991: Report from the Health and Safety Dept. to the GEB Chicago (Box 3, Folder 4)
- GEB 1991: Report from the Education Department to the GEB Chicago, Il., Oct. 15-18 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- GEB 1991: Report to the Education Committee of the GEB, January 15-18, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Jan. 15-18, 1991
- GEB 1991: Meeting of the GEB Educ. Committee, January 16, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Jan. 16, 1991
- GEB 1991: Report to the Education Comm. of the GEB, June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  June 25-27, 1991
- GEB 1992: GEB Report, September 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- GEB 1992: Report of the Education Dept. to the GEB (Box 3, Folder 10)
- GEB 1992: Research Department (Box 3, Folder 11)
- GEB 1992: Political Department Report to the GEB, 2/92 Miami (Box 3, Folder 12)
- GEB 1992: Benefit Funds Department Report to the GEB, 2/92 Miami, Fla. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- GEB 1992: Dept. of Associate Membership Report to the GEB, 2/92 Miami (Box 3, Folder 14)
- GEB 1992: Health and Safety Department Report to the GEB, 2/92 Miami (Box 3, Folder 15)
- GEB 1992: Report and Recommendations of the GEB Committee Merger of L246 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- GEB 1992: GEB Vancouver Meeting for September 15-22, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Sept. 15-22, 1992
- GEB 1992: GEB August 1992 Report Political/Education Dept. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Aug. 27, 12992
- Southwest District Council Report to the GEB, June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Report of the Political/Ed. Dept., Midwest region, June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Report of the Education Dept., Southern New England to GEB, June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Report of the Local 99 to the GEB meeting, June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Report of Puerto Rico region to GEB, June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Health and Safety Dept., Report to GEB, January 15-19, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  January 15-19, 1991
- Retiree Service Department Report to the GEB, January 15-19, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Report of Activities of the Dept. of International Rel., GEB, Jan. 15-19, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Jan. 15-19, 1991
- Associate ILGWU Member Report to the GEB, Jan. 15-19, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Political Department, Report to GEB, Jan. 15-19, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- GEB September 1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- GEB 1993 Report of Industry Devel. Working Group (Box 3, Folder 30)
- GEB 1993 Education Department Report (Box 3, Folder 31)
- GEB 1993 NAFTA materials (Box 3, Folder 32)
- GEB 1993 Financial Statement (Box 3, Folder 33)
- GEB 1993 Report of the Benefit Fund Dept. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Jan. 26, 1993
- GEB 1993: Aim Report (Box 4, Folder 2)
- GEB 1993: Research Department (Box 4, Folder 3)
- GEB Education Dept. Report, September 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Sept. 27-Oct. 1, 1993
- GEB 1993: Garment Industry Development Corp., January (Box 4, Folder 5)
- GEB June 1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- GEB June 1994 (continued) (Box 4, Folder 7)
- GEB February 1-4, 1994, Miami (Box 4, Folder 8)
  February 1-4, 1994
- GEB Reports, October 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- GIDC Classes (Box 4, Folder 10)
- GIDC: Garment Industry Development Corp. (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Grants Proposals: Grant Proposal - Bridges for PBS, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Grants Proposals: Grants Information, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Grants Proposals: Rutgers K-mart Grant Proposal (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Grants Proposals: Federal Dept. of Educ., Rutgers-ILGWU-NJ Labor Management 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Requisition forms for graphics, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Kitty Kruapt's Correspondence, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Memos to Kitty Krupat, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Incoming Letters, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Outgoing memos from Kitty Krupat, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Outgoing letters 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Incoming letters, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Memos from Kitty Krupat: Correspondence received, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Memos from Kitty Krupat, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Memos from Kitty Krupat: Internal memos/letters, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Letters from/to Kitty Krupat: 1992 internal memos (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Letters from/to Kitty Krupat: outgoing letters 1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Letters from/to Kitty Krupat: incoming memos 1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Letters from/to Kitty Krupat: outgoing memos 1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Letters from/to Kitty Krupat: 1993 correspondence received for K.K. (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Letters from/to Kitty Krupat: Outgoing memos/letters 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Letters from/to Kitty Krupat: memos/letters, outgoing, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Speeches: Hillary Rodham Clinton, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  June 3, 1993
- Speeches: Status of Haitian refugees, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  December 20, 1991
- Election 1992: Clinton administration position paper (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Election 1992: Presidential election material, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Publications from Locals/Regions: Local 23-25, 1990-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Publications from Locals/Regions: Local 89-22-1, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Publications from Locals/Regions: Local 99 News, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Publications from Locals/Regions: Local 155, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Publications from Locals/Regions: Chinatown Press, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Publications from Locals/Regions: Local 99, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  December 9, 1992
- Publications from Locals/Regions: Local 10 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Publications from Locals/Regions: Local 10 history (interview with Moe Diamond), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  March 1, 1974
- Publications from Locals/Regions: Local 23-25 Newsletter, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Union Worker - Northeast, Western PA, and Ohio Dept. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Canada Region - publications, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Locales 600-601, Puerto Rico, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Southwest District Council, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- ESL, New England, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  6/20/91
- Miscellaneous Materials, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- State Ties, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Steward Update (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Other materials from Locals/Regions: Canada Region, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Other materials from Locals/Regions: Puerto Rico, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Other materials from Locals/Regions: Local 99 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Other materials from Locals/Regions: ILGWU Northeast rank and file conference, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  August 28, 1990
- Other materials from Locals/Regions: Local 62-32, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Other materials from Locals/Regions: Outworkers News, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Other materials from Locals/Regions: Center for Law and Education, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  November 7, 1989
- ILGWU pamphlets, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Research Department, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Census 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Consumer Price Index, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Contract Enforcement - Gral. Guide, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Departments, Research: Apparel industry rests on economy, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Departments, Research: Public Speaking Workshop, Public Speaking Teaching (Box 8, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Departments, Research: The history of the ILGWU in songs and poems (Box 8, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Departments, Research: Penn & Schoen Associates (Box 8, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Departments, Research: Survey of Violations, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Health Care Campaign, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Health Care Campaign (continued), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Retiree Service Department: Classes, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Union Health Center: General Information (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Organizing Department: Organizing Activities, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Organizing Department: Strategic Planning Internal Organ Shop Case Study (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Organizing Department: Depart. Of Organization and F.S. (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Immigration Project: Local 99 Immigration Material (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Immigration Project: Amnesty Education Program (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Legislative Work: AFL-CIO Legislative Action Common. "A Grassroots Lobbying Manual", 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Legislative Work: Location of ILGWU Locals by States. and Congressional District 91-92, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Legislative Work: The Textile, Apparel and Footwear Trade Act of 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Legislative Work: H.R. 4496 Senate and House Textile/Apparel Bill, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Legislative Work: H.R. 3936 - Striker Replacement, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  May 3, 1990
- Legislative Work: Child Labor, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Legislative Work: Feb. 9, 1990 - Statement of Jay Mazur on the Caribbean Basin Economic Recovery Act (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Feb. 9, 1990
- Legislative Work: Disabilities Act 1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Legislative Work: Land Mark Decision - Electromation Teamsters 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Legislative Work: Employee Representation in a Non-Union Labor Market, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Health and Safety: Health and Safety Newsletter, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Health and Safety: News Articles on Health Care, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Health and Safety: Health and Safety in the '90s, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Health and Safety: Retreat Unity House, August 28-29, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Joint Union-University Committee on Labor Education: 1992 Memos, Letters, Drafts (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Joint Union-University Committee on Labor Education: Task-Force Volunteers, Survey Returns, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Joint Union-University Committee on Labor Education: 1992 AFL-CIO/UCLEA Annual Meeting, Pittsburgh (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Joint Union-University Committee on Labor Education: UCLEA/AFL-CIO Summer School for Union Women, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Joint Union-University Committee on Labor Education: Lists of Names and Numbers, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Women Issues: ILGWU Material on Reproductive R., 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Women Issues: Reproductive Rights Bulletin, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Women Issues: Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Women Issues: Women's Conference in Turkey, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Women Issues: Women Conference 1991 - Istanbul, Turkey (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Women Issues: CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  November 20, 1992
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: G.A.O., US General Accounting Office, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: Trinity Lutheran Seminary - The Institute for Mission in US (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: Report on the Americas (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: Time Magazine, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  April 9, 1990
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: Harvard Business Review, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: ACTWU (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: Asian American Free Labor Inst., 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: General Warehouse, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: OCAW (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Various Magazines, Bulletins, Statements: Literacy Assistance Center, Inc. - Monthly Calendar, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- BA Institute Central State Region - January 1992 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Business Agents Institute, Staff Development: Meeting, Feb. 20-24, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Business Agents Institute, Staff Development: Training, October 1-4, 1990, NYC (Box 10, Folder 20)
  October 1-4, 1990
- Business Agents Institute, Staff Development: Seminar, Feb. 20-24, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  Feb. 20-24, 1990
- Business Agents Institute, Staff Development - Business Agent Behavior (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Business Agents Institute, Staff Development: October 1-4, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2O)
- Organizers Training Seminar, Institute: ILGWU organizers' training (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Organizers Training Seminars, Institute: Organizing Directors Training Sub-Committee, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  October 10, 1990
- Education Directors Regional Conference: April 28-May 1, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  April 28-May 1, 1991
- Education Directors Regional Conference: Educational Programming, October 5-7, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  October 5-7, 1990
- Education Directors Regional Conference: Regional Seminar Staff, Puerto Rico, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Educational Directors Regional Conference: Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- National Educators Directors Conference, April 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- National Education Directors Conference/Meetings: National Education Directors Conference 1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- National Education Directors Conference, George Meany Center, March 1-4, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  March 1-4, 1992
- National Education Directors Conference, George Meany Center, March 1-4, 1992 (cont.) (Box 12, Folder 2)
- National Education Directors Conference, April 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Stewards Training Central States Region, July 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Steward Training, Puerto Rico, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Steward Training Program (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Leadership Program Exec. Board, Local 10, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Puerto Rico Education Department Training Report, April 8-18, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  April 8-18, 1992
- New England Staff Training Seminar, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  July 31, 1991
- ILGWU Media Training Seminar (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Contract Interpretation Training at Univ. Illinois 6/90, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Glasgow Operators Training, Sept.-Oct. 1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Mademoiselle Training 1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Mademoiselle Leadership Training 1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Sunset Park Leadership Training 1993 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- AIM, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- AIM Associate Membership (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Amnesty Education Program, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  October 15, 1992
- Benefit Committee: Education Plan (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Bulletins, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Consortium for Worker Education: Other matters, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Consortium for Worker Education: Budget Information, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)